Johnny Li

Software Developer

6675 Julie St. San Diego, CA 92115 (619) 564-1623 reptile18@gmail.com

CAREER SUMMARY

Software developer from San Diego with ten years of software development experience in the industry. Degree in Computer Science (B.S.) from UCSD with a minor in creative writing. Skilled in Java, C#, Python, Javascript, JQuery, Vue, React, and even lesser-known languages like InterSystems Cachè.

Strengths are completing development projects quickly, communicating frequently, and meeting deadlines. Successfully completed many wide-reaching projects and enhancements in my career. Looking forward to contributing meaningfully and bringing new features and optimizations to your organization.

LINKS

https://www.linkedin.com/in/johnny-li-031b949/https://github.com/reptile18 https://reptile18.github.io/Responsive-Portfolio/

EDUCATION

UCSD Extension Web Development Bootcamp - *Certificate*

Learning and developing projects in modern web frameworks (Node.js, React.js, MongoDB, Express, etc)

Mar 2020 - Sep 2020

University of California, San Diego - B.S. Computer Science

Coursework in Java SEP 2006 - JUL 2010 Minor in Creative Writing

SKILLS

Java, C#, HTML/CSS, Bootstrap, Git, ES6, JQuery, Vue.js, React.js,Node.js,Express.js Familiar with Issue Tracking software Strong written/verbal skills

EXPERIENCE

Covid - Can I Do It, Remote - Software Developer

MAR 2020 - Present

- Volunteer software development to a non-profit application that lets users assess risk associated with various activities as assessed by medical and public health experts.
- Created responsive components in Vue.js that fetches data from Google Firebase Realtime Database.
- Contributed feedback on technical aspects of the website in weekly meetings along with ideas on the direction of the project as well as future features.

Epic, Verona, WI - Software Developer

MAY 2013 - JUL 2019

- Significant enhancements to refill protocol decision support, allowing clinicians to quickly see the appropriateness of a medication refill request by displaying lab results, recent visits, conflicting medications, etc
- Contributed to a project that allowed physicians to work on outstanding tasks while viewing their schedule (such as viewing results, responding to patients electronically, and approving refills)
- Completed full stack projects and debugging in Intersystems Caché, VB6, .NET C#, Javascript, and CSS
- Used in-house proprietary software for issue tracking, documentation, and enhancement tracking
- Coordinated with a team of other developers, writers, and quality assurance

GDIT, San Diego, CA - Software Developer

JAN 2011 - APR 2013

- Powershell scripting and Java, Windows forms in C#
- Used Jira for issue tracking, documentation in Confluence
- Projects included scripting for VMs and real time data processing for threat detection